newchic.com 2016-11-29

# Privacy Policy - Newchic Help Center

Newchic.com respect the privacy of every visitor/customer of us. We take your online safety seriously. To better serve you and to help you understand how your information is used on our site, we have explained our privacy policy below.

 **1\. The information we collect**  
We believe it's vital for you to know what types of information we collect when you use our site. The information includes your Email, Name, Company Name, Street Address, Post Code, City, Country, Telephone Number, Password and so on. We collect these information in several different ways; to begin with, we use cookies which are needed to compile and aggregate non-personally identifiable information about the visitors to our site. Personally identifiable information consists of information which is unique to you, such as credit card number and bank account numbers. The information is unique to you.

 **2\. The use of information**  
To help us make our site more convenient for you to use by not entering information more than once.  
To help you quickly locate information, products, and services.  
To help us create content on this site which is most relevant to you.  
To remind you of new information, products, and services that we offer.  
After registering, you will receive our newsletters with information about sales, coupons, and special promotions. You can unsubscribe by using the link from any email newsletter or your personal subscribe setting after logged in.

 **Registration and Order:**  
During registration, you will be prompted to provide us with your name, shipping and billing address, phone number, email address and credit card number. In addition, we may also need your country so that we can comply with applicable laws and regulations, and we might need your gender as well. These types of personal information are used for billing purposes, to fulfill your orders, to communicate with you about your order and our site, and for internal marketing purposes. If we have problems when processing your order, we may use the personal information you provide to contact you.

 **Email Address:**  
You register for placing an order and receiving free promotional notices from us, we will notify you when we receive a new brand, or new product style. Your participation in a contest is completely voluntary, and you may choose whether to participate and disclose information to us.

 **3\. Privacy Security**  
We will not sell (or trade or rent) personally identifiable information to any person or any company as part of our regular course of business. We use the latest in encryption technology, and all employees that we do hire have to sign a confidentiality agreement that forbids them to disclose any information to other individuals or entities.

 **What kind of email do us send to our customers?**  
The email we send to our customers may include following:  
Transaction mail, Shipping notification, Weekly deal, Promotion, Activity.

 **How do I unsubscribe?**  
You can unsubscribe by using the link from any email newsletter or your personal subscribe setting after logged in.
